Matheus Chaves da Silva

Web developer

Contact:

Email: matheussilvachaves19@gmail.com

Telephone: (12) 99775-6151

State: São paulo

<u>City:</u> São José dos Campos Nighboard: Galo Branco

Address: Rua Clementino Rodrigues Simões 570

Professional links:

Personal Website: https://chaves3.github.io/ Repository: GitHub: GitHub - chaves3/chaves3

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/matheus-chaves-aa5600245

Profile:

Software developer with experience working on large projects at Aptiv, starting in development in 2021 as an apprentice where I stood out and was hired as an intern in the engineering laboratory. I recognize myself as an enthusiast of new technologies on the market, with learning acquired day after day. I focus on Web development, such as PHP, JavaScript and Python languages using MySQL database with SQL Server language, among other technologies that I use to create high-level and valuable web applications. I consider myself agile and consistent in learning a new language and adapting to any change, ready to overcome any challenge and evolve even more.

Professional history:

<u>Company:</u> Aptiv Position: Apprentice

Sector: IT

<u>Activities:</u> Technical support and development of web and desktop systems for improvements in all sectors in the factory using Visual Basic, C# and PHP languages. February 2021 Until February 2022

Company: Aptiv Position: Intern

Sector: Engineering laboratory

<u>Activities:</u> Data analysis with Python language using the Anaconda library with Jupyter, development of scripts in Python with Spider for electrical tests and development of web systems to improve the engineering laboratory sector with JavaScript and PHP languages

February 2022 Until July 2023

Freelancer

<u>Activities:</u> Development of web systems for first customers both on the front and back end, using MySQL database using JavaScipt and PHP languages. Actual job

Academic education:

High school: E.E. Dr. Pedro Mascarenhas - Completion in 2016

<u>Professional course: Administrative Assistant SENAI-SP-Santos dumount</u> – Completion in 2022

University education: Computer Engineering ETEP Esplanada: Completion in 2023

Extracurricular courses:

- PHP Jedai Danki Code
- Complete Web Master Front-end Course Danki Code
- Complete Web Development 2021 20 courses + 20 projects Udemy
- Data Scientist for Beginners 2021 + 2 Projects
- Python for Machine Learning and data science Didática Tech

Languages:

- Intermediate English: 2013 – 2015 – Microcamp

- Advanced English: 2024 - Private teacher

Featured project:

Link: https://produtos-quimicos-ambiente.000webhostapp.com/index.php

<u>Description:</u> System for controlling chemical products, where you can register, edit and delete all the chemicals at your disposal, you can download a table report of all chemicals in PDF and Excel and also has an alert that is sent to the administrator's email the chemical that is expired.

Technologies:

PHP, JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, Materialize, React (studying), Python, Visual Basic, MySql, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3